<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ECO 280</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on ECO 280</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 16:06:54 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>ECO 280 Syllabus</title>
      <link>/syllabus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 16:12:25 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/syllabus/</guid>
      <description>Susan Sayre | Smith College | Fall 2020
Course Description The course is designed to prepare students to conduct their own economic research or to work as part of research team. The course emphasizes practical research skills that complement existing coursework on economic theory and econometric methods. We focus on two main areas: effective strategies for searching, reading, and synthesizing the economic literature and practical data management, documentation, and wrangling skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homework 1: Setup and Git Basics</title>
      <link>/hw/hw1-git-basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 16:06:54 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hw/hw1-git-basics/</guid>
      <description>Submission details All steps should be completed no later than 10:30am EST on Mon 9/14, but I highly recommend aiming to have them done by Wed 9/9 so that your literature review repository will be available over the weekend. The specific steps:
 Follow the directions below to get Git, GitHub, R, RStudio and Stata working on your computer Commit and push at least a skeleton file to your lit-review-gitusername repo as described below Post at least one comment, question, or answer on the #hw1-git Slack channel Respond to my pinned &amp;ldquo;Is Stata installed on your computer?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Literature Review</title>
      <link>/assignment/lit-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 15:06:54 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/assignment/lit-review/</guid>
      <description>knitr::opts_chunk$set(echo = TRUE)Submission details You will submit this assignment by pushing a PDF of your literature review to your lit-review-gitusername repo by 10:30am EST on Wed Oct 7. Although not strictly required, it is highly recommended that you also push the sourcefile (e.g. a .docx or .Rmd file) unless you wrote your lit review in Google Docs.
There are several intermediate deadlines associated with this paper including:
 Wed Sep 16: Literature search description Wed Sep 23: Single article summary Mon Sep 28: Thematic grouping of papers Mon Sep 28 or Wed Sep 30: Mini-presentation  What I want you to do Write a synthetic review of the economic literature on a topic of your choosing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>This is a &amp;ldquo;hello world&amp;rdquo; example website for the blogdown package. The theme was forked from @jrutheiser/hugo-lithium-theme and modified by Yihui Xie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Course Projects</title>
      <link>/assignments/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/assignments/</guid>
      <description>There are three large projects in the course:
Due 10/7: Literature Review</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homework Assignments</title>
      <link>/homework/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/homework/</guid>
      <description>All assignments are due at 10:30am EST unless otherwise noted
Due 9/14: HW1 - Setup and Git Basics</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>